codyhouse.co 2019-08-22

# Privacy Policy | CodyHouse

This page informs you of Amber Creative Lab Ltd ("Amber Creative", “us”, “we”, or “our”) policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use the CodyHouse website (from now on “CodyHouse”). We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Cookies

When you visit CodyHouse, we put small files (known as ‘cookies’) onto your computer to collect information about how you browse the site.

Cookies are used to measure how you use the website so it can be updated and improved based on your needs.

Find out more about [how to manage cookies](https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/online/cookies/).

## Newsletter

If you subscribed to our newsletter, we shared your email address with [Mailchimp](https://mailchimp.com/), that is the email marketing service we use to create our newsletter campaigns. However, we will never share your email address with other third parties, and we will use it for the sole purpose of sending you emails about CodyHouse or other Amber Creative Lab news. If you wish to unsubscribe from our newsletter, you can do that by clicking the "unsubscribe" link in the footer of each newsletter, or by clicking the link below.

## Measuring website usage (Google Analytics)

We use Google Analytics software to collect information about how you use our website. We do this to help make sure the site is meeting the needs of its users and to help us make improvements. We don’t collect or store your personal information (for example your name or address) so this information can’t be used to identify who you are.

We don’t allow Google to use or share our analytics data.

Google Analytics sets the following cookies:

Name | Purpose | Expires   
---|---|---  
_ga | This helps us count how many people visit our website by tracking if you’ve visited before | 2 years  
_gid | This helps us count how many people visit our website by tracking if you’ve visited before | 24 hours  
_gat | Used to manage the rate at which page view requests are made | 10 minutes  
  
You can [opt out of Google Analytics cookies](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

## Information Sharing

We will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. We may share your personally identifiable information with third parties to provide and enhance your navigation through the website (e.g., if you subscribed to our newsletter, we will share your email address with MailChimp, that is the email marketing service we use to create our newsletter campaigns). If we do this, such third parties' use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy.

If you’re still unclear about our privacy policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://codyhouse.co/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Amber Creative Lab Ltd   
86-90 Paul Street   
London   
EC2A 4NE 

Project duplicated.
